Rădoi Victor-Andrei

J +40 (764) 347 095 | ☑ andreiradoi14@gmail.com | 🏠 rvandrei.com | 🛅 victorandreiradoi

About _

I am software professional with over 3 years of experience across diverse projects, ranging from mobile applications to specialized software solutions. As my career has progressed, I've increasingly taken on leadership responsibilities, discovering a natural aptitude for guiding teams, refining processes, and driving projects to success. With a solid foundation in technology and a growing passion for business and management, I'm eager to transition into roles where I have the opportunity to blend these skills effectively.

Skills _____

Data Analysis Python (PyTorch, Pandas, NumPy), SQL, R **Data Visualization** Tableau, Microsoft Excel (advanced), PowerBI

Agile Software Jira, Trello

Coding Java, Dart, Flutter, ReactJS, Unity, C++

Data Modeling, Requirements Gathering & Documentation, Stakeholder Management, Other

Wireframing, Presentation Skills

Education ____

Dublin City University

DUBLIN, IRELAND

MASTER'S DEGREE IN DATA ANALYTICS AND ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE September 2022 - June 2023

• Core Modules: Data Mining, Data Visualisation, Statistical Data Analysis, Machine Learning

• Core Modules: Software Engineering, Database Systems, Object Oriented Design

King's College London

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

LONDON, UNITED KINGDOM

September 2018 - June 2021

Experience _____

GoParty **REMOTE**

TECHNICAL PRODUCT OWNER

September 2023 - Present

- · Collaborated with founders to conceptualize and define the vision and roadmap for GoParty, an event ticketing solution, shaping the app's core functionalities and user experience from the ground up
- · Led the Beta testing phase, successfully coordinating 3 events with early adopters, resulting in a 85% positive feedback rate and actionable insights for product improvement
- · Worked closely with founders, developers, and designers to ensure alignment on product goals and user experience
- · Introduced agile practices, managing the product backlog and facilitating sprint planning and daily stand-ups. This improved team productivity and has so far reduced the projected time-to-market by 3 months

XOXNO REMOTE

MOBILE DEVELOPMENT LEAD (6 MONTHS CONTRACT)

December 2023 - May 2024

- Oversaw the internal launch of the XOXNO mobile app, an NFT marketplace on the MultiversX blockchain
- · Contributed to the implementation of new features, including a high-impact cryptocurrency transfer feature that enables users to securely transfer digital assets, integrating real-time transactions and multi-currency support
- · Led the refactoring of the initial codebase, resulting in a 30% reduction in technical debt and a more scalable architecture
- · Coordinated with UX/UI designers and backend developers to ensure alignment on product features and design

Teamboard REMOTE PROJECT LEAD January 2021 - March 2023

- Coordinated a small team of 5 and led the development of **Teamboard**, a sports club management platform
- · Managed end-to-end product development, from initial concept through to launch, overseeing all phases including design, development, testing, and deployment.
- · Was actively involved in the frontend development, implementing the main features of the application using Flutter
- · Maintained communication with over 30 sports clubs and coaches to gather requirements and identify new features
- · Led a product demonstration at the Romanian Basketball Federation's 2022 Annual Conference, showcasing the application's functions and securing its sale to a prominent sports club. The application quickly gained traction, surpassing 1,000 users at the time of sale

Evolution Labs BUCHAREST, ROMANIA

JUNIOR APPLICATION DEVELOPER

• Contributed to the development of the e-commerce application Carturesti, Romania's largest online bookstore

- · Worked closely with the UX team to translate AdobeXD mock-ups into responsive Flutter components
- Developed a specialized Flutter application integrated with Zebra scanners, streamlining the process of managing and tracking book inventory, which lead to a 30% reduction stock management time
- · Followed Scrum practices, participating in daily stand-ups, sprint planning, and retrospectives

Evonomix CONSTANTA, ROMANIA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN

March 2020 - September 2020

June 2021 - May 2022

• Designed and implemented a face filter application using advanced Augmented Reality (AR) techniques

- · Received mentorship and guidance in Unity development and AR tools from experienced professionals
- · Managed the project documentation, tracking technical challenges and solutions to support future development

Achievements _____

Awards PwC Academic Awards Winner (March 2024)



- Was awarded first place and received a monetary award for the best MSc Computing Practicum

Credit Suisse Coding Challenge (October 2019)

- Ranked top 20 out of over 200 participants



- ✓ Agile Requirements Foundations
- ✓ Requirements Elicitation and Analysis
- ✔ Project Management Foundations: Small Projects
- ✓ Master Clean Architecture in Flutter

Projects GestureXR (2023)



- Implemented a plugin that enables real-time freehand interaction in AR/VR settings
- Developed a ML algorithm for hand gesture recognition

AirQRunner (2021)

- Developed a mobile app that recommends optimal running routes by avoiding areas with high pollution

RezerWith (2020)

- Worked within a small team of developers to create an app that helped small businesses within the community during the Pandemic by digitally managing appointments